Welcome to Everyones Video.
This is the fastest way to add subtitles to any video.
We support six ASR engines from completely free to enterprise-grade.
The secret is our subtitle-first strategy. Most YouTube videos already have captions.
We grab those first. Only if they're missing do we call an ASR engine.
For Chinese content, FunASR from Alibaba DAMO Academy is free and nearly as good as paid APIs.
Once you have your SRT file, translate it to any language with a single command.
Then burn the subtitles right into the video. One script does it all.
Let's get started. Clone the repo and run setup.sh.
Your first subtitled video is five minutes away.